<DialogueTree xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
              xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/dialogue_schema.xsd">
    <NameField>Salmon</NameField>

    <DialogueNode>
        <Name>Start</Name>
        <EntryCondition>DEFAULT</EntryCondition>
        <Dialogue>
            <Page>Good morning, recruit! How'd you sleep?</Page>
        </Dialogue>
        <DialogueOptionsList>
            <DialogueOption>
                <Text>Good, I'm looking forward to making a difference!</Text>
                <DialogueTarget>Good Sleep</DialogueTarget>
            </DialogueOption>
            <DialogueOption>
                <Text>Ok, I'm a little nervous.</Text>
                <DialogueTarget>Ok Sleep</DialogueTarget>
            </DialogueOption>
            <DialogueOption>
                <Text>Not great, its so cold out here...</Text>
                <DialogueTarget>Bad Sleep</DialogueTarget>
            </DialogueOption>
        </DialogueOptionsList>
    </DialogueNode>

    <DialogueNode>
        <Name>Good Sleep</Name>
        <Dialogue>
            <Page>Glad to here it! We're always happy to have another helping hand.</Page>
        </Dialogue>
        <DialogueTarget>Mission</DialogueTarget>
    </DialogueNode>

    <DialogueNode>
        <Name>Ok Sleep</Name>
        <Dialogue>
            <Page>I understand, this will be a challenging and even dangerous job, but I'm sure you'll do great. We're happy to have you on board!</Page>
        </Dialogue>
        <DialogueTarget>Mission</DialogueTarget>
    </DialogueNode>

    <DialogueNode>
        <Name>Bad Sleep</Name>
        <Dialogue>
            <Page>To be honest, me too. It's still getting colder here, but we're not ready to move our base of operations yet. Thank you for being here.</Page>
        </Dialogue>
        <DialogueTarget>Mission</DialogueTarget>
    </DialogueNode>

    <DialogueNode>
        <Name>Mission</Name>
        <Dialogue>
            <Page>Now that you've completed your training, we'd like to welcome you to Outer Wilds Rescue!</Page>
            <Page>We have an important job for you...</Page>
            <Page>Evacuations are complete, and most of the new settlements are at least somewhat self-sufficient, but as I'm sure you're aware, conditions are not ideal.</Page>
            <Page>Environmental conditions make life difficult and everyone is packed into our few small settlements, and with the destruction of one of the Icy Ridge settlements we're all under stress right now.</Page>
            <Page>So we need you to act as a scout to find more suitable locations for settlements. You're free to investigate anywhere in the solar system that seems promising.</Page>
            <Page>Your ship has fantastic range and speed—I'd say it's our best work yet—so it should be able to get anywhere in the solar system.</Page>
            <Page>Where would do you plan on exploring first?</Page>
        </Dialogue>
        <DialogueOptionsList>
            <DialogueOption>
                <Text>I'll take another look at Ravenous Tides.</Text>
                <DialogueTarget>Tides</DialogueTarget>
            </DialogueOption>
            <DialogueOption>
                <Text>I think I'll explore here first.</Text>
                <DialogueTarget>Warm</DialogueTarget>
            </DialogueOption>
            <DialogueOption>
                <Text>I want to understand what happened on Icy Ridge.</Text>
                <DialogueTarget>Icy</DialogueTarget>
            </DialogueOption>
            <DialogueOption>
                <Text>I'm planning on visiting Icy Ridge's moon.</Text>
                <DialogueTarget>Moon</DialogueTarget>
            </DialogueOption>
            <DialogueOption>
                <Text>I'd like to investigate Sunbaked Stone.</Text>
                <DialogueTarget>Sunbaked</DialogueTarget>
            </DialogueOption>
            <DialogueOption>
                <Text>I'm not sure yet...</Text>
                <DialogueTarget>IDK</DialogueTarget>
            </DialogueOption>
        </DialogueOptionsList>
    </DialogueNode>

    <DialogueNode>
        <Name>Tides</Name>
        <Dialogue>
            <Page>Good idea! Our most successful settlement is on Ravenous Tides, and there may be more promising locations that have been overlooked.</Page>
        </Dialogue>
        <DialogueTarget>Exit</DialogueTarget>
    </DialogueNode>

    <DialogueNode>
        <Name>Warm</Name>
        <Dialogue>
            <Page>That's smart. There may be evidence here that could point to the cause of this ice age. Just don't forget your mission!</Page>
        </Dialogue>
        <DialogueTarget>Exit</DialogueTarget>
    </DialogueNode>

    <DialogueNode>
        <Name>Icy</Name>
        <Dialogue>
            <Page>We all do, what a horrible disaster. If we can understand why it happened maybe Icy Ridges could be a safer place for future settlements.</Page>
        </Dialogue>
        <DialogueTarget>Exit</DialogueTarget>
    </DialogueNode>

    <DialogueNode>
        <Name>Moon</Name>
        <Dialogue>
            <Page>Interesting plan. It hasn't seemed like a viable place for settlement, but with enough research maybe it could be.</Page>
        </Dialogue>
        <DialogueTarget>Exit</DialogueTarget>
    </DialogueNode>

    <DialogueNode>
        <Name>Sunbaked</Name>
        <Dialogue>
            <Page>Hmm, nobody had considered Sunbaked Stone as a viable location for settlement, but maybe we're wrong. I like how you think!</Page>
        </Dialogue>
        <DialogueTarget>Exit</DialogueTarget>
    </DialogueNode>

    <DialogueNode>
        <Name>IDK</Name>
        <Dialogue>
            <Page>That's ok, if you ask around I'm sure people could give you some ideas.</Page>
        </Dialogue>
        <DialogueTarget>Exit</DialogueTarget>
    </DialogueNode>

    <DialogueNode>
        <Name>Exit</Name>
        <Dialogue>
            <Page>Speak with Sunfish if you need any more help.</Page>
            <Page>—They're supposed to be out here briefing you with me, but you know how they get sucked into things.</Page>
            <Page>Go in through the back entrance, the stairs to the main entrance have collapsed again.</Page>
            <Page>And hey, you finished your training just before a planetary alignment! I think that's good luck</Page>
        </Dialogue>
    </DialogueNode>
</DialogueTree>